samma3a.com 2016-04-23

# Privacy Policy

This policy applies only to the activities on this website, and does not apply to activities that are offline or unrelated to the website.

**What information do we collect  and When? **

We collect information from you when you register on our site or place an order. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number.

## **What do we use your information for?  **

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * To personalize your experience: your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.
  * To improve our website: we continually work to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
  * To improve customer service: your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
  * To process transactions: Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

## **How do we protect your information?  **

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order, enter, submit, or access your account. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database.

Your private payment information (credit cards, financials, etc.) will NOT be stored on our servers, sold, shared, rented or leased to any third parties.

## **Do we use cookies?  **

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow)) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders by contacting customer service.

## **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?  **

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, as long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, to respond to a subpoena or court order, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

We may contain adverstising of third parties links to other sites, please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practicies or contents of theses sites nor for any third part to whom it transfers your data in accordance to this privacy policy.

## **Your acceptance of This policy**

By using our site, you automatically accept our privacy policy. If you have any concern about it, you can always contact us by sending an email to info@samma3a.com.

## **Changes to our Privacy Policy  **

The Website Policies and Terms & Conditions would be changed or updated occasionally to meet the requirements and standards. Therefore the Customers will be notified about these changes. Such modifications will become effective on the day they are posted, and we encourages you to frequently review the Privacy Policy for any modifications.

Updated on: 22-Oct-2014
